( theme music playing )
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Resync by lost0ne
3x03
Walk of Punishment
( arrow splashes )
( people coughing lightly )
( crowd murmuring )
( chuckles )
( exhales )
Edmure:
If I may. nephew.
I encountered a situation
with one of my lieutenants
at the Stone Mill
which may have some bearing--
Why don't you shut your mouth
about that damned mill?
And don't call him "nephew."
He is your king.
Robb knows
I meant him no disr--
You're lucky I'm not your king.
I wouldn't let you wave
your blunders around
like a victory flag.
My blunder sent Tywin's mad dog
scurrying back to Casterly Rock with
his tail between his legs.
I think King Robb understands
we're not gonna win this war
if he's the only one
winning any battles.
No. there's glory enough
to go around.
It's not about glory.
Your instructions were to wait
for him to come to you.
I seized an opportunity.
What value was the mill?
The Mountain was garrisoned
across the river from it.
Robb:
Is he there now?
Of course not.
We took the fight to him.
He could not withstand us.
I wanted to draw
the Mountain into the west.
into our country where
we could surround him and kill him.
I wanted him to chase us.
which he would have done
because he is a mad dog
without a strategic thought
in his head.
I could have that head
on a spike by now.
Instead. I have a mill.
Edmure:
We took hostages.
Willem Lannister.
Martyn Lannister.
Willem and Martyn Lannister
are 14 years old.
Martyn is 15. I believe.
Tywin Lannister has my sisters.
Have I sued for peace?
No.
Do you think
he'll sue for peace
because we have his father's
brother's
great-grandsons?
No.
How many men did you lose?
208.
But for every man we lost.
the Lannisters--
We need our men more
than Tywin needs his!
I'm sorry.
- I didn't know.
- You would have.
Right here today at this gathering
if you had been patient.
We seem to be running
short of patience here.
You know who isn't?
Tywin Lannister.
( Chains rattling )
( chair squeaking )
( sighs )
Intimate.
Lovely table.
Better chairs than the old
small council chamber.
Conveniently close
to your own quarters. I like it.
What news of Jaime?
20.000 unwashed Northerners
have known about
his escape for weeks.
Collectively. you control
more spies and informants
than the rest
of the world combined.
Do you mean to tell me
that none of you
has any notion of where he is?
- We are trying. my lord.
- Try harder.
What do we have. then?
Robb Stark and most of his
bannermen are in Riverrun
for the funeral of his grandfather
Lord Hoster Tully.
In Stark's absence.
Roose Bolton holds Harrenhal.
which would seem to make
him Lord of Harrenhal.
- in practice if not in name.
- Well. let him have it.
The name suits our purposes
far more than that
useless pile of rubble.
The Lord of Harrenhal will make a
worthy suitor for the widow Arryn.
For which I am extremely
grateful to you. my lord.
Lady Arryn and I have known
each other since we were children.
She has always been...
positively predisposed
toward me.
A successful courtship
would make Lord Baelish
acting Lord of the Vale.
Titles do seem to breed titles.
You'll leave for the Eyrie
as soon as possible
and bring Lysa Arryn
into the fold.
Then the young wolf can add
his own aunt to the list
of people who have
taken up arms against him.
Far be it from me
to hinder true love.
but Lord Baelish's absence
would present certain problems.
The royal wedding may end up
being the most expensive
event in living memory.
Summer has ended.
hard days lie ahead.
Not a good time to leave the
crown's finances unattended.
Tywin:
Fully agreed.
Which is why I'm naming you
new Master of Coin.
- ( Chuckles )
- Master of Coin?
It would appear to be a position
that best suits your talents.
I'm quite good
at spending money.
but a lifetime
of outrageous wealth
hasn't taught me much
about managing it.
I have no doubt you will
prove equal to this challenge.
Hear. hear.
Man: ♪ He lifted her
high in the air ♪
♪ He sniffed and roared
and smelled her there ♪
♪ She kicked and wailed.
a maid so fair ♪
♪ But he licked the honey
from her hair ♪
All: ♪ From there to here.
from here to there ♪
♪ All black and brown
and covered with hair ♪
♪ He smelled that girl
in the summer air ♪
♪ The bear. the bear
and the maiden fair... ♪
I hope you're pleased.
If you had armed me.
they never would have taken us.
You were armed
when we were taken.
I was in chains if you recall.
Our little match would
have ended quite quick
if my hands weren't bound.
All my life I've been
hearing. "Jaime Lannister.
what a brilliant swordsman."
You were slower
than I expected.
And more predictable.
I've been sitting
in a muddy pen
wrapped in chains
for the past year.
And I'm a woman.
I was still beating you.
You were not beating me.
Maybe you were as good
as people said...
once.
Or maybe people just love
to overpraise a famous name.
( Horse neighs )
When we make camp tonight.
you'll be raped.
More than once.
None of these fellows have
ever been with a noblewoman.
You'd be wise not to resist.
- Would I?
- They'll knock your teeth out.
You think I care
about my teeth?
No. I don't think you
care about your teeth.
If you fight them.
they will kill you.
Do you understand?
I'm the prisoner
of value. not you.
Let them have what they want.
What does it matter?
- What does it matter?
- Close your eyes.
Pretend they're Renly.
If you were a woman.
you wouldn't resist?
You'd let them
do what they wanted?
If I was a woman.
I'd make them kill me.
But I'm not. thank the gods.
If I had a proper forge.
I could make it good as new.
Doesn't have to look pretty.
It just has to keep
the arrows out of my heart.
Why are you helping him?
He takes us prisoner
and now he's our friend?
Thoros: You're not our prisoner.
little lady.
- What am I?
- Our guest.
No one's put any chains on you.
So I can walk away. then?
These woods aren't safe
for Ned Stark's daughter.
You're lucky we found you.
Hound: You think you're good with
that bow. you little twat?
Anguy: Better than anyone
you've ever met.
Hound:
A coward's weapon.
I like to fight up close.
I like to see a man's face
when I put the steel in him.
Why?
So you can kiss him?
You remember the last time
you were here?
Looks like every other
shit inn on the road.
Now. apologies.
but you're one ugly fucker
and I'd rather not
see you no more.
( Grunts )
Watch your head.
- ( Bangs wagon )
- Off we go.
- Man: Walk up!
- ( horse neighs )
What are you doing?
We're about to leave.
I'm staying.
You're what?
I baked some brown bread
for the innkeep
and she said
she never had better.
Told Thoros she's keeping me
as a payment
for all the free meals
she's given him.
Anyway. it's not me
the Brotherhood wants.
My brother ain't no king.
I'm not a Stark of Winterhell.
Winterfell.
- You sure?
- I'm sure.
Well. I made you something.
What is it?
It's a wolf.
Yes. it is.
That's the tail?
Yeah.
Well. be safe.
Yeah. you. too.
Don't get stabbed.
You don't...
burn your fingers.
Good-bye. Hot Pie.
Good-bye. Arry.
Up you go. little lady.
Arya:
Hey. Hot Pie.
It's really good.
A person could
almost be forgiven
for forgetting we're at war.
It often comforts me to think
that even in war's darkest days.
in most places in the world
absolutely nothing
is happening.
I've missed you. Uncle.
Father missed you. too.
from the day you left.
Maybe he never said it
in so many words--
Maybe?
Your father
was a stubborn old ox.
I was surprised when he died.
Didn't think death
had the patience.
I'm glad you were with him.
I wish to the gods I had been.
Did you make peace in the end?
After 30 years of fighting.
I don't think he remembered
what started it.
He asked me to stop
calling myself Blackfish.
He said it was an old joke
and it was never funny
to begin with.
I told him people had been
calling me Blackfish
for so long. they don't
remember my real name.
Every time he would leave
for the capital
or fight in a campaign.
I'd see him off.
"Wait for me.
little Cat." he'd say.
"Wait for me
and I'll come back
to you."
And I would sit at this window
every day when the sun
came up. waiting.
I wonder
how many times
did Bran or Rickon
stare across the moors
of Winterfell
waiting for me to return.
I will never see them again.
( crying )
You mustn't think it.
We don't know the truth.
They could be in hiding.
Robb believes they're alive.
And he must go on believing.
He's got to remain strong
if he's to prevail.
And you must remain
strong for him.
You're Robb Stark's wife.
Hold still.
Is it true
what they say about him?
I don't know.
What do they say about him?
That he can turn
into a wolf at night.
True.
And he eats the flesh
of his enemies.
True.
You're a Lannister. aren't you?
Martyn Lannister.
You've nothing to fear.
My husband
doesn't eat children.
Unless it's a full moon.
It's not a full moon
tonight. is it?
See?
Nothing to fear.
( fabric rips )
( wind howling )
Always the artists.
It's only horses.
No men.
You said there was dead crows.
There was.
How many men were here?
About 300.
And you know
what those men are now?
We're all the same to them--
meat for their army.
Do you think anyone got away?
Mance:
It's not impossible.
You don't go far
betting against Mormont.
But dead or alive.
he took a big gamble
coming north.
And he lost.
His best fighting men are dead.
And whether he's Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch
or a blue-eyed corpse.
he's a long way from home.
Tormund.
Climb the Wall.
Take Orell and 20 good men.
And take this one.
He knows Castle Black's
defenses better than any of us.
And if he's useful. good.
If not...
throw him off the Wall.
See if crows can fly.
We're finally going to war.
old friend?
Hide near Castle Black.
When I give the signal.
hit them in the night.
They've got a big old wall
to hide behind.
but it only guards one side.
( Chuckles )
- We'll meet again.
- Aye.
- If you do your job.
- Ah.
How will we see your signal?
Send your eagle above
the Wall every night.
When it's time. I'm going
to light the biggest fire
the North has ever seen.
( Coughing )
( donkey braying )
( women chatting )
( pigs squealing )
Ghost?
What have we here?
Frozen crows?
We've come a long way.
Craster: Smaller flock
than you went north with.
We can talk inside.
Oh. can we?
- ( Woman wailing )
- Woman ♪2: They need some water.
Tether it and I'll be inside.
( children coughing )
( woman moaning )
( pigs squealing )
( woman continues moaning )
Craster: Keep your eyes
where they belong.
They're not for you.
Bet you feed that pig
better than you feed us.
Aye. pig's got value to me.
You should all be kissing
my feet for letting you in.
I'd have turned you all away
if I wasn't a godly man.
You are a godly man?
I am.
I got no fear of what's out there.
When the white cold comes.
your swords and cloaks
and bloody fires won't help you.
The only ones left will be
those who are right with the gods.
The real gods.
( Woman wailing )
Go tell her she can
bite down on a rag
or she can bite down
on my fist.
Women.
( chuckles )
That sow right there gave birth
to a litter of eight.
Barely a grunt.
And she's almost as fat
as this one here.
Now why don't you dine on him?
Carve off what you need
as you go.
Well. look at him.
He's a walking feast.
( Squeals )
( Craster laughing )
- ( woman continues wailing )
- Woman ♪2: Here we are.
Sharpen these for me. would ya?
( woman continues wailing )
Woman #3: I see the head.
Push.
- ( wailing )
- That's it.
You're nearly there.
One more push should do it.
( Wailing )
( baby crying )
What is it?
( water dripping )
( door opens )
( breathing heavily )
Keep quiet.
( Groans )
( groans )
If you can't ride.
we don't stand a chance.
I can ride.
You're sure?
( Groans )
( groans )
Ride east.
Follow the rising sun.
Your sister's waiting for you.
I'll make you a Lord
of the Iron Islands for this.
We're not in the Iron Islands.
- Go.
- Come on.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Man:
Come on back.
Stannis: You refuse to tell me
where you're going?
Melisandre: I don't know yet.
The fires will show me.
- How long will you be gone?
- I don't know.
You're abandoning me.
I will never abandon you.
You are the Son of Fire.
- I am sworn to serve you.
- Then serve me.
When I return.
you will understand.
My enemies think
they've destroyed me.
They're laughing at me
the way Renly laughed at me.
I want Joffrey dead.
I want Robb Stark dead.
Make me another son.
I cannot.
Why?
You don't have the strength.
It would kill you.
I'm not so easily killed.
Men have been trying for years.
I want you.
Your fires burn low. my king.
There is another way.
A better way.
You told me your magic
requires a king's blood.
- Yes.
- I'm the one true king.
You are.
But there are others
with your blood in their veins.
You will sit
on the Iron Throne.
but first there must
be sacrifices.
The Lord of Light demands it.
( Birds screeching )
The Walk of Punishment
is a warning. Your Grace.
- To whom?
- To any slave who contemplates doing
whatever these slaves did.
Give me your water.
Khaleesi. this man
has been sentenced to death.
Here. drink.
( Mutters )
Barristan:
Leave this place. Your Grace.
Leave tonight. I beg you.
And what is she
to do for soldiers?
Barristan: We can find sellswords
in Pentos and Myr.
Is it "we" already.
Ser Barristan?
If you want to sit on the throne your
ancestors built. you must win it.
That will mean blood on your
hands before the thing is done.
The blood of my enemies.
not the blood of innocents.
Jorah: How many wars have you
fought in. Ser Barristan?
- Three.
- Have you ever seen a war
where innocents didn't die
by the thousands?
I was in King's Landing
after the sack. khaleesi.
You know what I saw?
Butchery.
Babies. children. old men.
More women raped
than you can count.
There's a beast in every man
and it stirs when you put
a sword in his hand.
But the Unsullied are not men.
They do not rape.
They do not put cities to the sword
unless they're ordered to do so.
If you buy them. the only men they'll
kill are those you want dead.
Do you disagree. Ser Barristan?
When your brother Rhaegar led
his army into battle at the Trident.
men died for him
because they believed in him.
because they loved him.
not because they'd been bought
at a slaver's auction.
I fought beside the last dragon
on that day. Your Grace.
I bled beside him.
Rhaegar fought valiantly.
Rhaegar fought nobly.
and Rhaegar died.
Did you know him well.
Ser Barristan?
I did. Your Grace.
Finest man I ever met.
I wish I had known him.
But he was not the last dragon.
All?
Did this one's ears
mishear. Your Grace?
They did not.
I want to buy them all.
_
There are 8.000 Unsullied
in Astapor.
Is this what you mean by all?
Yes. 8.000.
And the ones
still in training as well.
_
Master Greizhen says they
cannot sell half-trained boys.
If they fail
on the battlefield.
they will bring shame
upon all of Astapor.
I will have them all
or take none.
Many will fall in battle.
I'll need the boys to pick
up the swords they drop.
( Groans )
_
Master Kraznys says
you cannot afford this.
_
Your ship will buy you
100 Unsullied.
- ( Men laugh )
- Because Master Kraznys is generous.
The gold you have left
is worth 10.
But good Master Kraznys
will give you 20.
The Dothraki
you have with you--
_
The Dothraki you have are not
worth what they cost to feed.
but Master Kraznys will give
you three Unsullied
for all of them.
_
Master Kraznys asks
how you propose to pay
for the remaining
7.877 Unsullied.
I have dragons.
I'll give you one.
( Speaking Valyrian )
You will win the throne
with dragons. not slaves. Your Grace.
Khaleesi. please.
Three dragons.
- One.
- Two.
One.
( Whispering )
( speaks Valyrian )
Missandei:
They want the biggest one.
- Done.
I'll take you as well. now.
You'll be Master
Kraznys' gift to me.
A token of a bargain
well struck.
_
Khaleesi. a dragon is worth
more than any army.
Aegon Targaryen proved that.
You're both here to advise me.
I value your advice.
but if you ever question me
in front of strangers again.
you'll be advising
someone else.
Is that understood?
Do you have a name?
This one's name
is Missandei. Your Grace.
Do you have a family?
A mother and a father
you'd return to
if you had the choice?
No. Your Grace.
No family living.
You belong to me now.
It is your duty to tell me the truth.
Yes. Your Grace.
Lying is a great offense.
Many of those on the Walk of Punishment
were taken there for less.
I offered water to one of the slaves
dying on the Walk of Punishment.
Do you know what he said to me?
"Let me die."
There are no masters
in the grave. Your Grace.
Is it true what
Master Kraznys told me
about the Unsullied?
About their obedience?
All questions have been
taken from them.
They obey. that is all.
Once they are yours.
they are yours.
They will fall on their swords
if you command it.
And what about you?
You know that I'm taking you to war.
You may go hungry.
You may fall sick.
You may be killed.
Valar morghulis.
Yes. all men must die.
But we are not men.
Tyrion: A surprising place to keep
the royal ledgers.
Littlefinger:
I'm surprised you're surprised.
This is the safest place
in the city.
Not for bastards.
That's all of them. my lord.
Tyrion: Thank you. my dear.
Pod.
Take them outside.
- I'll be there in a moment.
- Yes. my lord.
I hear you owe that boy
a significant debt.
Only my life.
Not all that significant.
I'm afraid.
You should have him knighted.
If only the Master of Coin
had such power.
If only.
I owe you a significant debt.
Our redheaded friend.
You secured her release
when the queen detained her.
Oh. that.
Of course.
A simple misunderstanding.
Apparently. Her Grace believed
that you two had some sort
of special relationship.
We don't.
I did fuck her once.
- I know.
- But we don't.
I know.
But how would the queen
get that idea?
Why don't you ask her?
Any advice for me
on my new position?
Keep a low profile.
If I had a gold dragon
for every time I heard
that joke. I'd be richer than you are.
Well. you are richer than I am.
Good point.
They're only numbers.
Numbers on paper.
Once you understand that.
it's easy to make them behave.
Trivial even.
- You want a real challenge?
- ( women giggling )
Try whores.
I've tried quite a few.
Well. lots of work to do.
Enjoy the Eyrie.
Come on. I'm here later.
Come on.
Tonight. then.
Looks like dull reading.
Tyrion: You think all reading
is dull reading.
It's an opinion I share with
some of the finest men I know.
The secret history of the Seven
Kingdoms is written in these pages.
Unless Lord Twatbeard
made up a bunch of numbers
to hide what he's really up to.
Unless he made it all up. yes.
- Podrick. do keep up.
- Yes. my lord.
- Podrick.
- Yes. my lord?
After a long consultation
with my colleague Ser Bronn.
I finally found
a suitable reward
for the services you've
provided over and above
what might be
considered reasonable.
Tell me. Pod.
have you ever been
with a woman?
- No. my lord.
- Wonderful.
Genna specializes
in first-timers.
She's not bad with
second-timers. either.
Uh. my lord...
A fair enough repayment
for putting your spear
through my would-be killer's face.
wouldn't you say?
Now. as it happens.
Marei...
is quite the spear
handler herself.
She's here to thank you
for staying by my side
as the battle raged
all around me.
He's handsome.
You didn't tell me
he was handsome.
Kayla is famous
from here to Volantis
in certain circles.
One of four women in the world
who can perform a proper
Meereenese Knot.
My lord. I don't even...
She's here to thank you
for being a thoroughly
respectful fellow
who's never once failed
to address me as "my lord."
Be back in time for my supper.
Pace yourself. lad.
For years I've heard
that Littlefinger
is a magician.
Whenever the crown needs money.
he rubs his hands together
and. poof. mountains of gold.
Let me guess.
He's not a magician.
No.
- He's stealing it?
- Worse. he's borrowing it.
What's wrong with that?
We can't afford to pay it back.
that's what's wrong with it.
The crown owes millions
to my father.
Seeing as it's his grandson's
ass on the throne.
I imagine he'll forgive
that debt.
Forgive a debt. my father?
For a man of the world.
you're strangely naive.
I've never borrowed
money before.
I'm not clear on the rules.
Well...
Ahem!
The basic principle is
I lend you money.
and after an agreed upon
period of time.
you return it with interest.
And what if I don't?
Well. you have to.
But what if I don't?
This is why
I don't lend you money.
Anyway. it's not my father
I'm worried about.
It's the Iron Bank of Braavos.
We owe them tens of millions.
If we fail to repay these loans.
the bank will fund our enemies.
One way or another.
they always get their gold back.
( Door opens )
Ah. the return
of the conquering hero.
Does he have a little
jaunt in his step?
The lad's practically skipping.
You were gone a long time.
I trust you got
your money's worth.
Or should I say
my money's worth?
Oh. it was a gift. Podrick.
This is more than
I give you in a year.
He's a squire.
You don't pay him.
Oh. then it's much more
than I give you in a year.
They wouldn't take it. my lord.
Maybe they're trying
to curry some favor
with the new Master of Coin.
Have you ever known a whore
to turn down gold?
They were happy enough
to take it when I gave it to them.
What did you tell them?
I didn't tell them anything.
- What did you do to them?
- Lots of things.
And they seemed
to like these things?
Yes. my lord.
Of course
they seemed to like it.
They're paid
to seem to like it.
Only they weren't paid.
What are you saying?
These ladies enjoyed him so much.
they gave him
the time for free?
Is that what you're telling us?
Sit down. Podrick.
We're going to need details.
Copious details.
( Horse whinnies )
( whinnies )
- ( arrow whistles )
- ( gasps )
Come on!
Come on.
( Horse neighs )
Ha! Ha!
( Grunts )
- ( high-pitched ringing )
- ( gasping )
( neighs )
( gasping )
( grunts )
You know how we deal
with runaways here. do you?
( Groans )
Take off his pants.
- ( Men laughing )
- No! No!
No. no. no!
I'm gonna fuck you
into the dirt.
No. please!
No. no. no!
No. don't!
( Arrow thuds )
Theon:
No. please!
No! No!
- ( arrow whistles )
- ( groans )
You little bastard.
Come. my lord.
You're a long way from home
and winter is coming.
- ( Fire crackling )
- ( men chatting )
I'll take the big bitch first.
When she's good and wet.
you lot can finish her off.
My lord. I am Brienne of Tarth.
Lady Catelyn Stark commanded me
to deliver Ser Jaime
to King's Landing.
Catelyn Stark's
a treasonous cunt.
Orders were to take
the Kingslayer alive.
Nobody said shit about you.
- ( Grunts )
- ( shouts )
- ( blow lands )
- ( Brienne grunts )
You're only making it worse.
Locke: Take her over there
where it's dark.
I'd like a little privacy.
( Grunts )
- ( Brienne gasping )
- Come on!
( Screaming )
You know who she is. don't you?
A big dumb bitch
from who cares where.
Never been with
a woman that big.
Jaime:
She's Brienne of Tarth.
Her father
is Lord Selwyn Tarth.
Heard of Tarth?
Man:
I'm gonna cut your throat!
They call it the Sapphire Isle.
Do you know why?
Every sapphire in Westeros
was mined on Tarth.
Sapphires are gemstones.
- The blue ones.
- I know what they are.
Lord Selwyn would pay
his daughter's weight
in sapphires
if she's returned to him.
But only if she's alive.
her honor unbesmirched.
( Brienne screaming )
( men shouting )
Bring her back here.
Man:
Yes. my lord.
- Get up.
- Man ♪2: Come on.
Man #3:
Come on. on your feet.
Locke:
Unbesmirched.
Not defiled.
Fancy word for a fancy man.
I hated to read as a child.
but my father forced me
to study the books every morning
before I could practice
with sword or horse.
Two hours every day holed up in
the maester's chambers.
I learned a lot of fancy words.
I bet you did.
( Brienne screams )
Your father.
he'd pay your weight
in gold to get you back?
You'll be a rich man
till the end of your days.
And your sons will be rich men
and their sons after them.
Lands. titles--
you'll have them all.
The North can't win this war.
You're a smart man.
You understand that.
We have the numbers.
We have the gold.
Aye. you have both.
Fighting bravely
for a losing cause
is admirable.
Fighting for a winning cause
is far more rewarding.
Hard to argue with that.
Now that we're speaking
together man to man.
I wonder if you need
to keep me chained to this tree.
I'm not asking to be freed
from my constraints.
but if I could sleep
lying down.
my back would thank you for it.
I'm not as young
and resilient as I was once.
None of us are.
Locke: Unchain Ser Jaime
from the tree.
Man:
Come on. men.
Suppose you'll be wanting
something to eat.
I'm famished. actually.
Locke: I think we've got a spare
partridge on the fire.
Well. I do like partridge.
Bring the bird over here
and the carving knife.
Will this work
as a table. my lord?
Oh. yes.
Yes. this will do nic--
ah!
On the stump.
You think you're
the smartest man there is.
That everyone alive
has to bow and scrape
and lick your boots.
- My father--
- And if you get in any trouble.
all you've got to do
is say "my father"
and that's it.
all your troubles are gone.
- Don't.
- Have you got something to say?
Careful. You don't want to say
the wrong thing.
You're nothing
without your daddy.
and your daddy ain't here.
Never forget that.
Here. this should
help you remember.
( Screaming )
♪ A bear there was a bear.
a bear! ♪
♪ All black and brown
and covered with hair ♪
♪ Three boys. a goat.
and a dancing bear ♪
♪ They danced and spun
right to the fair ♪
♪ How sweet she was.
so pure and fair ♪
♪ The maid with honey
up in her hair ♪
♪ He smelled her all
in the summer air ♪
♪ The maid with honey
up in her hair ♪
♪ From there to here.
from here to there ♪
♪ All black and brown
and covered in hair ♪
♪ He smelled that girl
in the summer air ♪
- ♪ The bear. the bear ♪
- ♪ The maiden fair ♪
♪ Oh. I'm a maid
and I'm pure and fair ♪
♪ I'll never dance
with a hairy bear ♪
♪ I called a knight.
but you're a bear ♪
♪ All black and brown
and covered in hair ♪
♪ From there to here.
from here to there ♪
♪ All black and brown
and covered in hair ♪
♪ He smelled that girl
in the summer air ♪
- ♪ The bear. the bear ♪
- ♪ The maiden fair. ♪
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Resync by lost0ne